<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CompanyData>
    <CompanyIdentity>
        <Name>
            <FinalApprovedName>Pakiza Group</FinalApprovedName>
            <LegalNameVariations>Pakiza Group Ltd</LegalNameVariations>
            <ExactRawData>Pakiza Group</ExactRawData>
            <Sources>
                <Source>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</Source>
                <URL>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</URL>
                <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</Source>
                <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</URL>
                <Source>https://www.zoominfo.com/c/pakiza-group-ltd/369940779</Source>
                <URL>https://www.zoominfo.com/c/pakiza-group-ltd/369940779</URL>
                <Source>https://find-and-update.company-information.service.gov.uk/company/12862618/filing-history</Source>
                <URL>https://find-and-update.company-information.service.gov.uk/company/12862618/filing-history</URL>
                <Source>https://www.indiamart.com/pakiza-retailindore/registration-directors-info.html</Source>
                <URL>https://www.indiamart.com/pakiza-retailindore/registration-directors-info.html</URL>
            </Sources>
            <SourceNotes>Sources include official company website, LinkedIn, ZoomInfo, UK government's company filings, and IndiaMART. Each source provides different aspects of company identity.</SourceNotes>
            <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The final approved name is based on the most consistent and reliable sources, including the company's official website and LinkedIn profile. Variations are noted from other sources but are not considered primary.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
            <Status>OK</Status>
            <AnyRemainingIssues>No significant issues remain regarding the company name.</AnyRemainingIssues>
            <ProposedNextSteps>No further action is proposed for name verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
            <Notes>The company name is verified through multiple sources, ensuring a high level of confidence in its accuracy.</Notes>
            <NameVariationNotes>Minor variations in name presentation across sources do not affect the core identity of the company.</NameVariationNotes>
        </Name>
        <RegistrationDetails>
            <FinalRegistrationNumber>12862618</FinalRegistrationNumber>
            <FinalRegistrationDate>Not available</FinalRegistrationDate>
            <ExactRawData>12862618</ExactRawData>
            <Sources>
                <Source>https://find-and-update.company-information.service.gov.uk/company/12862618/filing-history</Source>
                <URL>https://find-and-update.company-information.service.gov.uk/company/12862618/filing-history</URL>
            </Sources>
            <SourceNotes>The UK government's company filings are considered the most authoritative source for registration details.</SourceNotes>
            <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The registration number is verified through the official UK government registry. However, the registration date could not be found, indicating a need for further research or clarification from official sources.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
            <Status>NEEDS_REVIEW</Status>
            <AnyRemainingIssues>The registration date is not available, which may be necessary for a complete company profile.</AnyRemainingIssues>
            <ProposedNextSteps>Attempt to find the registration date through official channels or contact the company directly for this information.</ProposedNextSteps>
            <Notes>The registration number is confirmed, but the lack of a registration date limits the completeness of the registration details.</Notes>
            <RegistrationNumberNotes>No variations in the registration number were found across sources.</RegistrationNumberNotes>
            <RegistrationDateNotes>The absence of a registration date in available sources is a notable gap in the company's registration details.</RegistrationDateNotes>
        </RegistrationDetails>
        <CompanyStatus>Active</CompanyStatus>
        <CompanyStatusNotes>The company's active status is verified through the UK government's company filings, indicating ongoing operations.</CompanyStatusNotes>
        <BusinessEntityType>Private Limited Company by guarantee without share capital use of 'Limited' exemption</BusinessEntityType>
        <BusinessEntityTypeNotes>The business entity type, as verified through official government registry, indicates a specific legal structure that may influence operational and financial aspects of the company.</BusinessEntityTypeNotes>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>The company identity section is largely complete, with the exception of the registration date, which requires further investigation.</Notes>
        <IdentityVerificationProcess>The verification process involved cross-checking information across multiple sources, including official registries, the company's website, and social media profiles, to ensure accuracy and reliability.</IdentityVerificationProcess>
    </CompanyIdentity>

    <ContactInformation>
        <Email>info@pakizagroup.com</Email>
        <EmailNotes>The email address is verified through the company's website and LinkedIn profile, indicating an active and potentially responsive point of contact.</EmailNotes>
        <Phone>+880 1725402739</Phone>
        <PhoneNotes>The phone number is verified through an independent directory and cross-checked with the company website, providing a means of direct communication.</PhoneNotes>
        <Website>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</Website>
        <WebsiteNotes>The company website is functional, providing information on products, services, and company details, and serves as a primary source for company information.</WebsiteNotes>
        <SocialMediaProfiles>
            <Platform>Not available</Platform>
            <URL>Not available</URL>
            <ProfileNotes>No social media profiles were found or verified for Pakiza Group.</ProfileNotes>
        </SocialMediaProfiles>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</URL>
            <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</Source>
            <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</URL>
            <Source>https://www.zoominfo.com/c/pakiza-group-ltd/369940779</Source>
            <URL>https://www.zoominfo.com/c/pakiza-group-ltd/369940779</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources for contact information include the company's website, LinkedIn, and ZoomInfo, each providing different contact details.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Contact information is compiled from multiple sources to ensure accuracy and provide multiple means of contact.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No significant issues remain regarding contact information.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further action is proposed for verifying contact information.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Contact information is verified and appears accurate, facilitating communication with the company.</Notes>
        <ContactConsistencyNotes>Contact information is consistent across sources, enhancing confidence in its accuracy.</ContactConsistencyNotes>
    </ContactInformation>

    <Headquarters>
        <Address>House# 97, Road# 11/A, Dhaka-1209, Bangladesh</Address>
        <ExactRawData>House# 97, Road# 11/A, Dhaka-1209, Bangladesh</ExactRawData>
        <AddressComponentNotes>No inconsistencies were found in the address components across sources.</AddressComponentNotes>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</URL>
            <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</Source>
            <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The company's website and LinkedIn profile are considered reliable sources for headquarters address information.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The headquarters address is verified through multiple sources, ensuring its accuracy.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No issues remain regarding the headquarters address.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further action is proposed for verifying the headquarters address.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>The headquarters address is confirmed, providing a physical location for the company.</Notes>
        <GeographicVerificationNotes>No geographic verification was conducted beyond confirming the address through multiple sources.</GeographicVerificationNotes>
        <HeadquartersHistoryNotes>No information is available on changes in headquarters location.</HeadquartersHistoryNotes>
    </Headquarters>

    <LocationsAndOperations>
        <AdditionalLocations>Not available</AdditionalLocations>
        <AdditionalLocationsNotes>No information is available on additional locations beyond the headquarters.</AdditionalLocationsNotes>
        <FactoryLocations>Not available</FactoryLocations>
        <FactoryLocationsNotes>No specific information is available on factory locations.</FactoryLocationsNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Not available</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>Not available</Source>
            <URL>Not available</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>No sources provide comprehensive information on additional locations or factory locations.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The lack of information on additional locations and factory locations indicates a need for further research or direct inquiry to the company.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>NO_DATA</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>Significant gaps remain in information regarding additional locations and operations.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Attempt to find information through company reports, industry directories, or direct contact with the company.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>This section is incomplete due to a lack of available data on additional locations and factory locations.</Notes>
        <LocationVerificationMethodNotes>No methods were applied for verifying locations beyond the headquarters due to insufficient data.</LocationVerificationMethodNotes>
        <GeographicDistributionNotes>No analysis can be provided on the geographic distribution of company operations due to limited information.</GeographicDistributionNotes>
    </LocationsAndOperations>

    <Industry>
        <FinalIndustryClassification>Textiles</FinalIndustryClassification>
        <IndustryClassificationNotes>The industry classification is based on information from the company's website and LinkedIn profile, indicating primary involvement in textiles.</IndustryClassificationNotes>
        <MainProductsOrServices>Spinning, Dyeing, Knitting, Weaving</MainProductsOrServices>
        <ProductsServicesNotes>These services are noted as primary offerings of the company, based on its website and LinkedIn profile.</ProductsServicesNotes>
        <Certifications>
            <Certification>Not available</Certification>
            <CertificationSource>Not available</CertificationSource>
            <CertificationDate>Not available</CertificationDate>
            <CertificationNotes>No certification information is available for Pakiza Group.</CertificationNotes>
        </Certifications>
        <CertificationsOverviewNotes>No overview can be provided due to the lack of certification information.</CertificationsOverviewNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Textiles</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</URL>
            <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</Source>
            <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The company's website and LinkedIn profile are primary sources for industry and product/service information.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The industry classification and main products/services are determined based on consistent information from reliable sources.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No significant issues remain regarding industry classification and main products/services.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further action is proposed for verifying industry and product/service information.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>The industry and main products/services are identified with a reasonable level of confidence based on available sources.</Notes>
        <IndustryTrendsNotes>No specific trends are noted due to the lack of detailed industry analysis.</IndustryTrendsNotes>
        <CompetitivePositionNotes>No information is available to assess the company's competitive position within its industry.</CompetitivePositionNotes>
    </Industry>

    <OwnershipDetails>
        <ParentCompany>Not available</ParentCompany>
        <ParentCompanyNotes>No information is available on a parent company for Pakiza Group.</ParentCompanyNotes>
        <Owner>Not available</Owner>
        <OwnershipStructureNotes>No detailed ownership structure information is available, including shareholders or ownership percentages.</OwnershipStructureNotes>
        <KeyDirectors>Rafiqul Islam Khan, Reajul Islam Khan, Rakibul Islam Khan</KeyDirectors>
        <KeyDirectorsNotes>These individuals are noted as key executives based on information from the company's website and LinkedIn profile.</KeyDirectorsNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Rafiqul Islam Khan, Reajul Islam Khan, Rakibul Islam Khan</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.pakizagroup.com/</URL>
            <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</Source>
            <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/pakiza-group</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The company's website and LinkedIn profile provide information on key executives.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The identification of key directors is based on information from reliable sources, but the lack of detailed ownership structure information limits the understanding of the company's ownership.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>NEEDS_REVIEW</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>Significant gaps remain in ownership details, including parent company and shareholder information.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Attempt to find information through official corporate filings, business registries, or direct contact with the company.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>This section is incomplete due to the lack of available data on ownership structure and parent company.</Notes>
        <BeneficialOwnershipNotes>No information is available to identify ultimate beneficial owners.</BeneficialOwnershipNotes>
        <CorporateGovernanceNotes>No specific information is available on the company's governance structure or board composition beyond key executives.</CorporateGovernanceNotes>
    </OwnershipDetails>

    <FinancialInformation>
        <Revenue>$4 million</Revenue>
        <RevenueNotes>The revenue figure is based on a single source and may require validation through official financial reports or a reputable financial database.</RevenueNotes>
        <ProfitBeforeTax>Not available</ProfitBeforeTax>
        <ProfitNotes>No profit information is available.</ProfitNotes>
        <MarketValue>Not available</MarketValue>
        <MarketValueNotes>No market value information is available for Pakiza Group.</MarketValueNotes>
        <StockInformation>Not available</StockInformation>
        <StockPerformanceNotes>As a private limited company, stock information and performance are not applicable.</StockPerformanceNotes>
        <ExactRawData>$4 million</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://rocketreach.co/pakiza-group-ltd-profile_b45dbefefc60e98b</Source>
            <URL>https://rocketreach.co/pakiza-group-ltd-profile_b45dbefefc60e98b</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The revenue figure is from a single source and may not reflect the company's current financial situation accurately.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The financial information is limited, with only revenue partially verified through a single source, indicating a need for more comprehensive and reliable financial data.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>NEEDS_REVIEW</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>Significant gaps remain in financial information, including profit, market value, and detailed revenue figures.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Attempt to find information through official financial reports, reputable financial databases, or direct contact with the company.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>This section is largely incomplete due to the lack of available and verified financial data.</Notes>
        <FinancialHealthNotes>No assessment can be made of the company's financial health due to insufficient data.</FinancialHealthNotes>
        <FinancialReportingNotes>No information is available on the quality, transparency, or timeliness of the company's financial reporting.</FinancialReportingNotes>
    </FinancialInformation>

    <DataAssessmentSummary>
        <OverallDataQuality>The overall data quality is mixed, with some sections having reliable and verified information, while others lack sufficient data or have inconsistencies.</OverallDataQuality>
        <DataQualityNotes>Factors affecting data quality include the availability of reliable sources, inconsistencies across sources, and the lack of detailed information in certain areas such as financials and ownership structure.</DataQualityNotes>
        <MajorGaps>Major gaps include detailed financial information, ownership structure, parent company information, and comprehensive industry analysis.</MajorGaps>
        <DataGapsNotes>These gaps impact the ability to fully assess the company's operations, financial health, and market position, highlighting the need for further research or direct inquiry to the company.</DataGapsNotes>
        <RecommendedNextSteps>Recommended next steps include attempting to find missing information through official corporate filings, business registries, industry reports, or direct contact with the company, and validating existing information through multiple sources where possible.</RecommendedNextSteps>
        <NextStepsNotes>Prioritizing the acquisition of detailed financial reports, verifying ownership structure through official sources, and conducting a comprehensive industry analysis are key next steps.</NextStepsNotes>
        <Notes>The data collection process highlighted the importance of verifying information through multiple sources and the challenges of obtaining comprehensive data on private companies.</Notes>
        <ResearchProcessNotes>The research process involved a systematic review of available sources, including company websites, social media, official registries, and industry directories, with an emphasis on verifying information through reliable and independent sources.</ResearchProcessNotes>
        <ConfidenceLevelNotes>The confidence level in the data varies by section, with higher confidence in verified contact information and company identity, and lower confidence in areas with limited or unverified data such as financials and ownership.</ConfidenceLevelNotes>
        <FinalRecommendationNotes>A final recommendation would be to approach any business decisions with caution due to the gaps in information, and to prioritize the collection of comprehensive and verified data to support decision-making.</FinalRecommendationNotes>
    </DataAssessmentSummary>
</CompanyData>