<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CompanyData>
    <CompanyIdentity>
        <Name>
            <FinalApprovedName>Ha-Meem Group</FinalApprovedName>
            <LegalNameVariations>Ha-meem Group</LegalNameVariations>
            <ExactRawData>Ha-Meem Group</ExactRawData>
            <Sources>
                <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</Source>
                <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</URL>
                <Source>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ha-meem_Group</Source>
                <URL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ha-meem_Group</URL>
                <Source>https://textilepages.com/ha-meem-group</Source>
                <URL>https://textilepages.com/ha-meem-group</URL>
                <Source>https://www.dnb.com/business-directory/company-profiles.ha-meem_textiles_limited.be2d419c53fb1141e125547b86b5965f.html</Source>
                <URL>https://www.dnb.com/business-directory/company-profiles.ha-meem_textiles_limited.be2d419c53fb1141e125547b86b5965f.html</URL>
                <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/About.html</Source>
                <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/About.html</URL>
                <Source>https://www.eximpedia.app/companies/ha-meem-group-new-york-us/07496101</Source>
                <URL>https://www.eximpedia.app/companies/ha-meem-group-new-york-us/07496101</URL>
                <Source>https://contactout.com/company/Ha-Meem-Group-9895</Source>
                <URL>https://contactout.com/company/Ha-Meem-Group-9895</URL>
                <Source>https://digitalmag.theceomagazine.com/delwar-hossain/</Source>
                <URL>https://digitalmag.theceomagazine.com/delwar-hossain/</URL>
                <Source>https://www.textileinfomedia.com/business-info/Hameem-Group</Source>
                <URL>https://www.textileinfomedia.com/business-info/Hameem-Group</URL>
            </Sources>
            <SourceNotes>Sources are a mix of official company websites, industry directories, and news articles, providing a comprehensive view of the company's name and identity.</SourceNotes>
            <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The final approved name is selected based on the consistency across multiple reliable sources, including the company's official website and reputable industry directories.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
            <Status>OK</Status>
            <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with the company name.</AnyRemainingIssues>
            <ProposedNextSteps>No further steps are proposed for the company name verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
            <Notes>The company name is consistently represented across all sources, indicating a high level of confidence in the name's accuracy.</Notes>
            <NameVariationNotes>No significant name variations were found, suggesting a stable and consistent brand identity.</NameVariationNotes>
        </Name>
        <RegistrationDetails>
            <FinalRegistrationNumber>Not available</FinalRegistrationNumber>
            <FinalRegistrationDate>Not available</FinalRegistrationDate>
            <ExactRawData>Not available</ExactRawData>
            <Sources>
                <Source>No URL source found</Source>
                <URL>No URL source found</URL>
            </Sources>
            <SourceNotes>No reliable sources were found for registration details, indicating a need for further research or direct contact with the company.</SourceNotes>
            <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Given the lack of available information, registration details could not be verified through publicly available sources.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
            <Status>NO_DATA</Status>
            <AnyRemainingIssues>Registration number and date are not available, which could be crucial for certain business or legal purposes.</AnyRemainingIssues>
            <ProposedNextSteps>Direct contact with the company or access to private databases may be necessary to obtain registration details.</ProposedNextSteps>
            <Notes>The absence of registration information in public sources may indicate privacy measures or the need for specialized access to business registries.</Notes>
            <RegistrationNumberNotes>No registration number was found, which could impact the verification of the company's legal status.</RegistrationNumberNotes>
            <RegistrationDateNotes>No registration date was available, making it difficult to determine the company's age or history.</RegistrationDateNotes>
        </RegistrationDetails>
        <CompanyStatus>Active</CompanyStatus>
        <CompanyStatusNotes>The company is described as active by multiple sources, including its official website and industry directories, indicating ongoing operations.</CompanyStatusNotes>
        <BusinessEntityType>Conglomerate in textile and garments sector</BusinessEntityType>
        <BusinessEntityTypeNotes>The company operates as a conglomerate, focusing on the textile and garments sector, which suggests a diversified approach within a specific industry.</BusinessEntityTypeNotes>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>The company identity section is largely complete, with the exception of registration details, which are not publicly available.</Notes>
        <IdentityVerificationProcess>The verification process involved cross-checking information across multiple sources to confirm the company's name, status, and business entity type.</IdentityVerificationProcess>
    </CompanyIdentity>

    <ContactInformation>
        <Email>delwar@hameemgroup.com, delwerp2000@yahoo.com</Email>
        <EmailNotes>Emails were found on the company's contact page, but their validity or responsiveness is unverified.</EmailNotes>
        <Phone>+880-2-8170592, +880-2-8170593, +880-2-8170583</Phone>
        <PhoneNotes>Phone numbers are provided on the company's website, but their accuracy or current status is not confirmed.</PhoneNotes>
        <Website>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</Website>
        <WebsiteNotes>The website appears to be active and provides basic information about the company, its products, and contact details.</WebsiteNotes>
        <SocialMediaProfiles>
            <Platform>Not available</Platform>
            <URL>Not available</URL>
            <ProfileNotes>No social media profiles were found, which may indicate a limited online presence beyond the official website.</ProfileNotes>
        </SocialMediaProfiles>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/contact-us.html</Source>
            <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/contact-us.html</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The primary source for contact information is the company's official website, which may not be comprehensive or up-to-date.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Contact information was gathered from the company's website and appears to be the most direct source for this data.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No issues were found with the contact information available, but its accuracy is unverified.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Verification of contact information through direct contact or additional research may be necessary for confirmation.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Contact information is available but should be verified for accuracy and responsiveness.</Notes>
        <ContactConsistencyNotes>Contact information is consistent across the sources that provide it, but this is largely limited to the company's website.</ContactConsistencyNotes>
    </ContactInformation>

    <Headquarters>
        <Address>387 (South), Tejgaon Industrial Area, Dhaka-1208, Bangladesh</Address>
        <ExactRawData>387 (South), Tejgaon Industrial Area, Dhaka-1208, Bangladesh</ExactRawData>
        <AddressComponentNotes>The address is consistently reported across multiple sources, suggesting a high degree of accuracy.</AddressComponentNotes>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</URL>
            <Source>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ha-meem_Group</Source>
            <URL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ha-meem_Group</URL>
            <Source>https://textilepages.com/ha-meem-group</Source>
            <URL>https://textilepages.com/ha-meem-group</URL>
            <Source>https://www.dnb.com/business-directory/company-profiles.ha-meem_textiles_limited.be2d419c53fb1141e125547b86b5965f.html</Source>
            <URL>https://www.dnb.com/business-directory/company-profiles.ha-meem_textiles_limited.be2d419c53fb1141e125547b86b5965f.html</URL>
            <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/About.html</Source>
            <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/About.html</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources include the company's website, industry directories, and Wikipedia, providing a robust confirmation of the headquarters' location.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The headquarters' address is verified through multiple sources, ensuring a high level of confidence in its accuracy.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No issues were found with the headquarters' address.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further verification is proposed for the headquarters' address.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>The headquarters' address is well-documented and consistent across sources, indicating a reliable piece of information.</Notes>
        <GeographicVerificationNotes>Geographic verification through mapping services could further confirm the address's accuracy and provide additional context about the location.</GeographicVerificationNotes>
        <HeadquartersHistoryNotes>No information is available on changes to the headquarters' location, suggesting stability in the company's primary location.</HeadquartersHistoryNotes>
    </Headquarters>

    <LocationsAndOperations>
        <AdditionalLocations>Ashulia, Savar</AdditionalLocations>
        <AdditionalLocationsNotes>These locations are mentioned as part of the company's operations, possibly indicating manufacturing or distribution sites.</AdditionalLocationsNotes>
        <FactoryLocations>Ashulia, Savar</FactoryLocations>
        <FactoryLocationsNotes>Factory locations suggest where the company's production activities are based, which could be important for supply chain and operational considerations.</FactoryLocationsNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Ashulia, Savar</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.daily-sun.com/post/768448</Source>
            <URL>https://www.daily-sun.com/post/768448</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The source for additional locations is limited, suggesting a need for further research to confirm the company's operational footprint.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Locations were identified through a single source, which may not provide a comprehensive view of the company's operations.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>NEEDS_REVIEW</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>The accuracy and completeness of location information could be improved with additional sources or verification.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Further research or direct confirmation with the company could help verify and expand the list of locations.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>While some location information is available, it is not comprehensive and requires further verification for accuracy and completeness.</Notes>
        <LocationVerificationMethodNotes>Verification of locations could involve cross-checking with multiple sources, including industry reports, news articles, and official company communications.</LocationVerificationMethodNotes>
        <GeographicDistributionNotes>The geographic distribution of the company's operations could provide insights into its market reach, supply chain, and strategic positioning.</GeographicDistributionNotes>
    </LocationsAndOperations>

    <Industry>
        <FinalIndustryClassification>Textile and garments sector</FinalIndustryClassification>
        <IndustryClassificationNotes>The industry classification is based on the company's primary products and services, which are consistently reported across sources.</IndustryClassificationNotes>
        <MainProductsOrServices>Readymade garments, denim fabric</MainProductsOrServices>
        <ProductsServicesNotes>These products are central to the company's operations and are mentioned in various sources, including the company's website and industry directories.</ProductsServicesNotes>
        <Certifications>
            <Certification>Not available</Certification>
            <CertificationSource>No URL source found</CertificationSource>
            <CertificationDate>Not available</CertificationDate>
            <CertificationNotes>No certification information was found, which could be important for quality control, regulatory compliance, and market access.</CertificationNotes>
        </Certifications>
        <CertificationsOverviewNotes>The lack of available certification information may indicate a need for further research or direct inquiry with the company.</CertificationsOverviewNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Textile and garments sector</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</URL>
            <Source>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ha-meem_Group</Source>
            <URL>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ha-meem_Group</URL>
            <Source>https://textilepages.com/ha-meem-group</Source>
            <URL>https://textilepages.com/ha-meem-group</URL>
            <Source>https://www.dnb.com/business-directory/company-profiles.ha-meem_textiles_limited.be2d419c53fb1141e125547b86b5965f.html</Source>
            <URL>https://www.dnb.com/business-directory/company-profiles.ha-meem_textiles_limited.be2d419c53fb1141e125547b86b5965f.html</URL>
            <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/About.html</Source>
            <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/About.html</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources consistently report the company's involvement in the textile and garments sector, providing a clear industry classification.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Industry classification is determined based on the company's products and services, as reported by multiple sources.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No issues were found with the industry classification.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further verification is proposed for the industry classification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>The company's industry classification is well-supported by multiple sources, indicating a high level of confidence in this information.</Notes>
        <IndustryTrendsNotes>Understanding industry trends could provide insights into the company's growth prospects, challenges, and strategic positioning within the textile and garments sector.</IndustryTrendsNotes>
        <CompetitivePositionNotes>The company's competitive position within its industry could be assessed through market share, product quality, pricing strategy, and innovation, among other factors.</CompetitivePositionNotes>
    </Industry>

    <OwnershipDetails>
        <ParentCompany>Not available</ParentCompany>
        <ParentCompanyNotes>No information is available on a parent company, which could indicate that Ha-Meem Group operates independently or the information is not publicly disclosed.</ParentCompanyNotes>
        <Owner>Not available</Owner>
        <OwnershipStructureNotes>No details are available on the ownership structure, which could be important for understanding the company's control, decision-making processes, and potential conflicts of interest.</OwnershipStructureNotes>
        <KeyDirectors>AK Azad (Managing Director), Lt. Col. Md. Delwar Hossain PSC (retd.) (Group Deputy Managing Director)</KeyDirectors>
        <KeyDirectorsNotes>Key directors are identified, but their roles, responsibilities, and backgrounds could provide additional insights into the company's leadership and governance.</KeyDirectorsNotes>
        <ExactRawData>AK Azad (Managing Director), Lt. Col. Md. Delwar Hossain PSC (retd.) (Group Deputy Managing Director)</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/contact-us.html</Source>
            <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/contact-us.html</URL>
            <Source>https://digitalmag.theceomagazine.com/delwar-hossain/</Source>
            <URL>https://digitalmag.theceomagazine.com/delwar-hossain/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources provide some information on key personnel, but the ownership structure and parent company details are not available.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Ownership details and key directors are identified through limited sources, indicating a need for further research for a comprehensive understanding.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>NEEDS_REVIEW</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>The lack of information on the parent company and ownership structure could be significant for certain business or investment decisions.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Direct inquiry with the company or access to private databases may be necessary to obtain detailed ownership information.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>While some information on key directors is available, the ownership structure and parent company details are not publicly disclosed, limiting the understanding of the company's governance and control.</Notes>
        <BeneficialOwnershipNotes>Identifying beneficial owners could be challenging due to the lack of publicly available information on the company's ownership structure.</BeneficialOwnershipNotes>
        <CorporateGovernanceNotes>The company's corporate governance practices, including board composition and executive compensation, are not detailed in publicly available sources.</CorporateGovernanceNotes>
    </OwnershipDetails>

    <FinancialInformation>
        <Revenue>$550 million (turnover)</Revenue>
        <RevenueNotes>Revenue is reported in a single source, which may not reflect the company's current financial situation or provide a comprehensive view of its financial performance.</RevenueNotes>
        <ProfitBeforeTax>Not available</ProfitBeforeTax>
        <ProfitNotes>No profit information is available, which could be important for assessing the company's financial health and profitability.</ProfitNotes>
        <MarketValue>Not available</MarketValue>
        <MarketValueNotes>No market value information is available, which could indicate a private company or limited public disclosure of financial data.</MarketValueNotes>
        <StockInformation>Not available</StockInformation>
        <StockPerformanceNotes>No stock information is available, suggesting the company may not be publicly traded or the information is not publicly disclosed.</StockPerformanceNotes>
        <ExactRawData>$550 million (turnover)</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.hameemgroup.net/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The source for financial information is limited, providing only revenue data and no detailed financial statements or analysis.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Financial information is gathered from a single source, which may not provide a complete or up-to-date picture of the company's financial situation.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>NEEDS_REVIEW</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>The lack of comprehensive financial information could limit the assessment of the company's financial health, profitability, and growth prospects.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Further research or direct contact with the company may be necessary to obtain more detailed and current financial information.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Financial information is limited and primarily based on a single source, indicating a need for additional research or disclosure to fully understand the company's financial position.</Notes>
        <FinancialHealthNotes>The available financial information does not provide a comprehensive view of the company's financial health, making it difficult to assess its stability or growth potential.</FinancialHealthNotes>
        <FinancialReportingNotes>The company's financial reporting practices, including transparency and timeliness, cannot be fully evaluated due to the limited availability of financial data.</FinancialReportingNotes>
    </FinancialInformation>

    <DataAssessmentSummary>
        <OverallDataQuality>The overall data quality is mixed, with some sections having comprehensive and reliable information, while others lack detail or have uncertain accuracy.</OverallDataQuality>
        <DataQualityNotes>Data quality issues stem from the limited availability of certain types of information, such as financial data, ownership structure, and certification details.</DataQualityNotes>
        <MajorGaps>Major gaps include detailed financial information, ownership structure, parent company details, and comprehensive certification data.</MajorGaps>
        <DataGapsNotes>These gaps could impact the ability to fully assess the company's financial health, governance, and operational capabilities.</DataGapsNotes>
        <RecommendedNextSteps>Recommended next steps include further research, potentially involving direct contact with the company, to fill in the gaps in information and verify the accuracy of available data.</RecommendedNextSteps>
        <NextStepsNotes>Priority should be given to obtaining detailed financial statements, clarifying the ownership structure, and identifying any parent company or significant shareholders.</NextStepsNotes>
        <Notes>The data collection process highlighted the importance of diverse and reliable sources for each aspect of company data, including financials, ownership, and operations.</Notes>
        <ResearchProcessNotes>The research process involved a review of publicly available sources, including the company's website, industry directories, and news articles, to gather and verify information.</ResearchProcessNotes>
        <ConfidenceLevelNotes>The confidence level in the data varies by section, with higher confidence in areas like company identity and industry classification, and lower confidence in areas with limited or no information.</ConfidenceLevelNotes>
        <FinalRecommendationNotes>A final recommendation would depend on the specific purposes of the data assessment, but generally, caution should be exercised in areas where data is limited or uncertain, and further verification should be sought when possible.</FinalRecommendationNotes>
    </DataAssessmentSummary>
</CompanyData>