<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CompanyData>
    <CompanyIdentity>
        <Name>
            <FinalApprovedName>Epyllion Group</FinalApprovedName>
            <LegalNameVariations>Epyllion Group</LegalNameVariations>
            <ExactRawData>Epyllion Group</ExactRawData>
            <Sources>
                <Source>https://www.epylliongroup.com/</Source>
                <URL>https://www.epylliongroup.com/</URL>
                <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</Source>
                <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</URL>
                <Source>https://disclosures.ifc.org/project-detail/SII/42000/epyllion-knit</Source>
                <URL>https://disclosures.ifc.org/project-detail/SII/42000/epyllion-knit</URL>
                <Source>https://unglobalcompact.org/what-is-gc/participants/16284-Epyllion-Group</Source>
                <URL>https://unglobalcompact.org/what-is-gc/participants/16284-Epyllion-Group</URL>
                <Source>https://abstractapi.com/companyenrichment?domain=epylliongroup.com</Source>
                <URL>https://abstractapi.com/companyenrichment?domain=epylliongroup.com</URL>
            </Sources>
            <SourceNotes>Sources are a mix of official company websites, social media, and business directories, providing a good balance of primary and secondary information.</SourceNotes>
            <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The final approved name is based on the consistent naming across all sources, with no significant variations found.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
            <Status>OK</Status>
            <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with the company name.</AnyRemainingIssues>
            <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions needed for name verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
            <Notes>Name verification was straightforward due to the consistency across sources.</Notes>
            <NameVariationNotes>No significant name variations were found, indicating a strong brand identity.</NameVariationNotes>
        </Name>
        <RegistrationDetails>
            <FinalRegistrationNumber>Not provided</FinalRegistrationNumber>
            <FinalRegistrationDate>1994</FinalRegistrationDate>
            <ExactRawData>1994</ExactRawData>
            <Sources>
                <Source>https://abstractapi.com/companyenrichment?domain=epylliongroup.com</Source>
                <URL>https://abstractapi.com/companyenrichment?domain=epylliongroup.com</URL>
                <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</Source>
                <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</URL>
            </Sources>
            <SourceNotes>Year of founding is confirmed by multiple sources, but exact registration details are not provided.</SourceNotes>
            <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The year of founding is used as a proxy for registration date due to the lack of specific registration information.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
            <Status>NO_DATA</Status>
            <AnyRemainingIssues>Registration number and exact date are not available.</AnyRemainingIssues>
            <ProposedNextSteps>Attempt to find official registration documents or contact the company directly for more information.</ProposedNextSteps>
            <Notes>Registration details are incomplete due to the lack of publicly available information.</Notes>
            <RegistrationNumberNotes>No registration number was found in the available sources.</RegistrationNumberNotes>
            <RegistrationDateNotes>The year of founding is confirmed, but the exact registration date is not available.</RegistrationDateNotes>
        </RegistrationDetails>
        <CompanyStatus>Active</CompanyStatus>
        <CompanyStatusNotes>The company is actively operating, as indicated by its website and recent updates on social media.</CompanyStatusNotes>
        <BusinessEntityType>Private Limited Company</BusinessEntityType>
        <BusinessEntityTypeNotes>The business entity type is inferred from the company's structure and operations but is not explicitly stated in the sources.</BusinessEntityTypeNotes>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Company identity information is mostly complete, with some gaps in registration details.</Notes>
        <IdentityVerificationProcess>Verification involved cross-checking information across multiple sources, including official company websites and social media.</IdentityVerificationProcess>
    </CompanyIdentity>

    <ContactInformation>
        <Email>info@epylliongroup.com</Email>
        <EmailNotes>Email address is provided on the company's website and is presumed to be active.</EmailNotes>
        <Phone>+88-02-9840223</Phone>
        <PhoneNotes>Phone number is provided on the company's website but has not been verified as active.</PhoneNotes>
        <Website>https://www.epylliongroup.com</Website>
        <WebsiteNotes>The website is active and provides comprehensive information about the company.</WebsiteNotes>
        <SocialMediaProfiles>
            <Platform>LinkedIn</Platform>
            <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</URL>
            <ProfileNotes>The LinkedIn profile is active and provides updates on the company's activities.</ProfileNotes>
        </SocialMediaProfiles>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.epylliongroup.com/contact-us.php</Source>
            <URL>https://www.epylliongroup.com/contact-us.php</URL>
            <Source>https://www.epylliongroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.epylliongroup.com/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources for contact information are primarily the company's official website and social media profiles.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Contact information is verified through the company's official channels.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with contact information.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions needed for contact information verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Contact information is readily available and appears to be up-to-date.</Notes>
        <ContactConsistencyNotes>Contact information is consistent across different sources.</ContactConsistencyNotes>
    </ContactInformation>

    <Headquarters>
        <Address>227/A Tejgaon-Gulshan Link Road, Dhaka-1208, Bangladesh</Address>
        <ExactRawData>227/A Tejgaon-Gulshan Link Road, Dhaka-1208, Bangladesh</ExactRawData>
        <AddressComponentNotes>No inconsistencies found in the address components.</AddressComponentNotes>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.epylliongroup.com/contact-us.php</Source>
            <URL>https://www.epylliongroup.com/contact-us.php</URL>
            <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</Source>
            <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</URL>
            <Source>https://zoominfo.com/c/epyllion-group/354067119</Source>
            <URL>https://zoominfo.com/c/epyllion-group/354067119</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources confirm the headquarters address consistently.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The headquarters address is verified through multiple sources, including the company's website and social media.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with the headquarters address.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions needed for headquarters address verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Headquarters address is confirmed through multiple reliable sources.</Notes>
        <GeographicVerificationNotes>No geographic verification was performed beyond confirming the address through multiple sources.</GeographicVerificationNotes>
        <HeadquartersHistoryNotes>No information is available on changes in the headquarters location.</HeadquartersHistoryNotes>
    </Headquarters>

    <LocationsAndOperations>
        <AdditionalLocations>No additional locations provided.</AdditionalLocations>
        <AdditionalLocationsNotes>No information is available on additional office locations beyond the headquarters.</AdditionalLocationsNotes>
        <FactoryLocations>No factory locations provided.</FactoryLocations>
        <FactoryLocationsNotes>No information is available on factory or production sites.</FactoryLocationsNotes>
        <ExactRawData>No exact location data beyond headquarters is available.</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.epylliongroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.epylliongroup.com/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Information on locations and operations is limited to the headquarters address.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Locations and operations information is based on the available data, which is primarily focused on the headquarters.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>NO_DATA</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>Additional locations and factory locations are not available.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Attempt to find more detailed information on the company's operations and locations.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Information on locations and operations is incomplete.</Notes>
        <LocationVerificationMethodNotes>No location verification was performed due to the lack of detailed location information.</LocationVerificationMethodNotes>
        <GeographicDistributionNotes>No information is available to assess the geographic distribution of the company's operations.</GeographicDistributionNotes>
    </LocationsAndOperations>

    <Industry>
        <FinalIndustryClassification>Retail Apparel and Fashion</FinalIndustryClassification>
        <IndustryClassificationNotes>Industry classification is based on the company's products and services.</IndustryClassificationNotes>
        <MainProductsOrServices>Garments, Textiles</MainProductsOrServices>
        <ProductsServicesNotes>Products and services are as stated on the company's website and other sources.</ProductsServicesNotes>
        <Certifications>No certifications provided.</Certifications>
        <CertificationsOverviewNotes>No information is available on certifications.</CertificationsOverviewNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Retail Apparel and Fashion</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</Source>
            <URL>https://www.linkedin.com/company/epylliongroup</URL>
            <Source>https://abstractapi.com/companyenrichment?domain=epylliongroup.com</Source>
            <URL>https://abstractapi.com/companyenrichment?domain=epylliongroup.com</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Industry information is consistent across the available sources.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Industry classification is based on the products and services offered by the company.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with industry classification.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions needed for industry classification verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Industry information is consistent and well-documented.</Notes>
        <IndustryTrendsNotes>No information is available on current industry trends and their impact on the company.</IndustryTrendsNotes>
        <CompetitivePositionNotes>No information is available to assess the company's competitive position within its industry.</CompetitivePositionNotes>
    </Industry>

    <OwnershipDetails>
        <ParentCompany>No parent company information provided.</ParentCompany>
        <ParentCompanyNotes>No information is available on a parent company.</ParentCompanyNotes>
        <Owner>Mr. Reaz Uddin Al-Mamoon (45.8%), Mr. Md. Kishwar Jahan</Owner>
        <OwnershipStructureNotes>Ownership structure is based on the available single source.</OwnershipStructureNotes>
        <KeyDirectors>No key directors information provided.</KeyDirectors>
        <KeyDirectorsNotes>No information is available on key directors or executives.</KeyDirectorsNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Mr. Reaz Uddin Al-Mamoon (45.8%), Mr. Md. Kishwar Jahan</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://disclosures.ifc.org/project-detail/SII/42000/epyllion-knit</Source>
            <URL>https://disclosures.ifc.org/project-detail/SII/42000/epyllion-knit</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Ownership information is based on a single source and may not be comprehensive or up-to-date.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Ownership details are as provided by the single available source.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>SINGLE_SOURCE</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>Ownership information is based on a single source and may require further verification.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Attempt to find more sources to verify and expand on the ownership information.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Ownership information is limited and based on a single source.</Notes>
        <BeneficialOwnershipNotes>No information is available on beneficial ownership beyond the provided ownership structure.</BeneficialOwnershipNotes>
        <CorporateGovernanceNotes>No information is available on corporate governance structure or practices.</CorporateGovernanceNotes>
    </OwnershipDetails>

    <FinancialInformation>
        <Revenue>$67.5 million</Revenue>
        <RevenueNotes>Revenue figure is based on the available sources and may not reflect the current financial situation.</RevenueNotes>
        <ProfitBeforeTax>No profit before tax information provided.</ProfitBeforeTax>
        <ProfitNotes>No information is available on profit before tax.</ProfitNotes>
        <MarketValue>No market value information provided.</MarketValue>
        <MarketValueNotes>No information is available on market value.</MarketValueNotes>
        <StockInformation>No stock information provided.</StockInformation>
        <StockPerformanceNotes>No information is available on stock performance.</StockPerformanceNotes>
        <ExactRawData>$67.5 million</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://rocketreach.co/epyllion-group-profile_b5dd999ef42e5534</Source>
            <URL>https://rocketreach.co/epyllion-group-profile_b5dd999ef42e5534</URL>
            <Source>https://apparelresources.com/business-news/sourcing/epyllion-groups-growth-strategy-less-competition-automation-motivation/</Source>
            <URL>https://apparelresources.com/business-news/sourcing/epyllion-groups-growth-strategy-less-competition-automation-motivation/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Financial information is limited and based on the available sources.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>Financial information is as provided by the sources and may require further verification and updating.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>Financial information is incomplete and may not reflect the current situation.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Attempt to find more comprehensive and up-to-date financial information.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NEEDS_REVIEW</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>Financial information is limited and based on available sources.</Notes>
        <FinancialHealthNotes>No assessment of financial health can be made due to the lack of comprehensive financial information.</FinancialHealthNotes>
        <FinancialReportingNotes>No information is available on the quality and transparency of the company's financial reporting.</FinancialReportingNotes>
    </FinancialInformation>

    <DataAssessmentSummary>
        <OverallDataQuality>Variable</OverallDataQuality>
        <DataQualityNotes>Data quality varies across sections, with some information being well-documented and other areas lacking detail or verification.</DataQualityNotes>
        <MajorGaps>Registration details, locations and operations, ownership structure, and financial information are areas with significant gaps or limitations.</MajorGaps>
        <DataGapsNotes>These gaps may impact the overall assessment and decision-making processes, as they limit the understanding of the company's operations, structure, and financial situation.</DataGapsNotes>
        <RecommendedNextSteps>Further research and verification are recommended to address the identified gaps and improve the overall data quality.</RecommendedNextSteps>
        <NextStepsNotes>Prioritized actions should focus on obtaining official registration documents, detailed location and operations information, comprehensive ownership structure, and up-to-date financial data.</NextStepsNotes>
        <Notes>The data collection process highlighted the importance of verifying information through multiple sources and the need for more detailed data in several areas.</Notes>
        <ResearchProcessNotes>The research involved reviewing available sources, including company websites, social media, business directories, and financial reports, with an emphasis on cross-verifying information whenever possible.</ResearchProcessNotes>
        <ConfidenceLevelNotes>Confidence in the data varies, with higher confidence in areas like company identity and contact information, and lower confidence in areas with limited or single-source information.</ConfidenceLevelNotes>
        <FinalRecommendationNotes>A comprehensive review and verification process is recommended before making any decisions based on this data, due to the identified gaps and limitations.</FinalRecommendationNotes>
    </DataAssessmentSummary>
</CompanyData>