<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CompanyData>
    <CompanyIdentity>
        <Name>
            <FinalApprovedName>Square Textiles Ltd</FinalApprovedName>
            <LegalNameVariations>Square Textiles Ltd</LegalNameVariations>
            <ExactRawData>Square Textiles Ltd</ExactRawData>
            <Sources>
                <Source>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</Source>
                <URL>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</URL>
                <Source>https://squaregroup.com/bussiness/square-textiles-ltd/</Source>
                <URL>https://squaregroup.com/bussiness/square-textiles-ltd/</URL>
                <Source>https://mccibd.org/mcci_members/square-textiles-ltd/</Source>
                <URL>https://mccibd.org/mcci_members/square-textiles-ltd/</URL>
                <Source>https://linkedin.com/company/square-textiles-ltd-</Source>
                <URL>https://linkedin.com/company/square-textiles-ltd-</URL>
                <Source>https://bb.linkedin.com/company/squaretextilesdivision</Source>
                <URL>https://bb.linkedin.com/company/squaretextilesdivision</URL>
                <Source>https://www.amarstock.com/stock/SQUARETEXT</Source>
                <URL>https://www.amarstock.com/stock/SQUARETEXT</URL>
            </Sources>
            <SourceNotes>Sources are official company websites, business directories, and social media profiles, which are considered reliable for name information.</SourceNotes>
            <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The final approved name was selected based on consistency across multiple reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
            <Status>OK</Status>
            <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with company name data.</AnyRemainingIssues>
            <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions proposed for company name verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
            <Notes>No notes on name verification process, as the information was consistent and reliable across sources.</Notes>
            <NameVariationNotes>No name variations were observed across the sources, indicating a consistent company identity.</NameVariationNotes>
        </Name>
        <RegistrationDetails>
            <FinalRegistrationNumber>Not available</FinalRegistrationNumber>
            <FinalRegistrationDate>October 15, 1994</FinalRegistrationDate>
            <ExactRawData>October 15, 1994</ExactRawData>
            <Sources>
                <Source>https://roc.portal.gov.bd/</Source>
                <URL>https://roc.portal.gov.bd/</URL>
                <Source>https://squaregroup.com/document/view/49/Square_Textile_AR_2023_0EkP2N1.pdf</Source>
                <URL>https://squaregroup.com/document/view/49/Square_Textile_AR_2023_0EkP2N1.pdf</URL>
            </Sources>
            <SourceNotes>The registration date was confirmed through official documents and a government database, but the registration number remains unavailable due to its absence on the official company registry.</SourceNotes>
            <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The registration date was verified through multiple sources, including official documents and a government database, while the registration number's unavailability was noted due to its absence on the official company registry.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
            <Status>NO_DATA</Status>
            <AnyRemainingIssues>The registration number for Square Textiles Ltd could not be found on the official company registry or government database.</AnyRemainingIssues>
            <ProposedNextSteps>Further investigation into alternative sources for the registration number is proposed.</ProposedNextSteps>
            <Notes>The registration number's unavailability may indicate a need for deeper investigation into company registration details.</Notes>
            <RegistrationNumberNotes>The registration number was not found on the official company registry or government database, which may require further investigation.</RegistrationNumberNotes>
            <RegistrationDateNotes>The registration date was confirmed through official documents and a government database, ensuring the accuracy of this information.</RegistrationDateNotes>
        </RegistrationDetails>
        <CompanyStatus>Active</CompanyStatus>
        <CompanyStatusNotes>The company status was validated through multiple independent sources, including the company website and business directories.</CompanyStatusNotes>
        <BusinessEntityType>Public Limited Company</BusinessEntityType>
        <BusinessEntityTypeNotes>The business entity type was noted as a Public Limited Company based on information from reliable sources.</BusinessEntityTypeNotes>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>No notes on company identity verification, as the information was consistent and reliable across sources.</Notes>
        <IdentityVerificationProcess>The company identity was verified through official company websites, business directories, and social media profiles, ensuring a reliable and consistent identity.</IdentityVerificationProcess>
    </CompanyIdentity>

    <ContactInformation>
        <Email>textiles@squaregroup.com</Email>
        <EmailNotes>The email address was verified through multiple sources, including the company website and business directories.</EmailNotes>
        <Phone>Not available</Phone>
        <PhoneNotes>No phone number was available from the provided sources.</PhoneNotes>
        <Website>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</Website>
        <WebsiteNotes>The website was verified as active and providing relevant company information.</WebsiteNotes>
        <SocialMediaProfiles>
            <Platform>LinkedIn</Platform>
            <URL>https://linkedin.com/company/square-textiles-ltd-</URL>
            <ProfileNotes>The LinkedIn profile was verified as active and providing relevant company information.</ProfileNotes>
        </SocialMediaProfiles>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</URL>
            <Source>https://mccibd.org/mcci_members/square-textiles-ltd/</Source>
            <URL>https://mccibd.org/mcci_members/square-textiles-ltd/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources are official company websites and business directories, which are considered reliable for contact information.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The contact information was verified through multiple reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with contact information.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions proposed for contact information verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>No notes on contact information verification, as the information was consistent and reliable across sources.</Notes>
        <ContactConsistencyNotes>The contact information was consistent across multiple sources, indicating reliable and up-to-date information.</ContactConsistencyNotes>
    </ContactInformation>

    <Headquarters>
        <Address>Square Center, 48 Mohakhali C/A, Dhaka-1212, Bangladesh</Address>
        <ExactRawData>Square Center, 48 Mohakhali C/A, Dhaka-1212, Bangladesh</ExactRawData>
        <AddressComponentNotes>No inconsistencies were noted in the address components.</AddressComponentNotes>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</URL>
            <Source>https://mccibd.org/mcci_members/square-textiles-ltd/</Source>
            <URL>https://mccibd.org/mcci_members/square-textiles-ltd/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources are official company websites and business directories, which are considered reliable for address information.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The headquarters address was verified through multiple reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with headquarters data.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions proposed for headquarters verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>No notes on address verification, as the information was consistent and reliable across sources.</Notes>
        <GeographicVerificationNotes>No geographic verification was performed, as the address was verified through reliable sources.</GeographicVerificationNotes>
        <HeadquartersHistoryNotes>No changes in headquarters location were noted.</HeadquartersHistoryNotes>
    </Headquarters>

    <LocationsAndOperations>
        <AdditionalLocations>Saradaganj, Kashimpur, Gazipur, Bangladesh</AdditionalLocations>
        <AdditionalLocationsNotes>The factory location was updated with a new source.</AdditionalLocationsNotes>
        <FactoryLocations>Saradaganj, Kashimpur, Gazipur, Bangladesh</FactoryLocations>
        <FactoryLocationsNotes>The factory location was updated with a new source, indicating a reliable and up-to-date location.</FactoryLocationsNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Saradaganj, Kashimpur, Gazipur, Bangladesh</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://www.tritechbd.com/portfolio/square-textile/</Source>
            <URL>https://www.tritechbd.com/portfolio/square-textile/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The source is a reliable website providing information on the company's factory location.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The factory location was verified through a reliable source, indicating a trustworthy location.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with location data.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions proposed for location verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>No notes on location verification, as the information was consistent and reliable across sources.</Notes>
        <LocationVerificationMethodNotes>The location was verified through a reliable source, indicating a trustworthy location.</LocationVerificationMethodNotes>
        <GeographicDistributionNotes>No patterns in geographic distribution were noted, as only one location was verified.</GeographicDistributionNotes>
    </LocationsAndOperations>

    <Industry>
        <FinalIndustryClassification>Textile</FinalIndustryClassification>
        <IndustryClassificationNotes>The industry classification was determined through reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</IndustryClassificationNotes>
        <MainProductsOrServices>Cotton yarn, denim fabrics</MainProductsOrServices>
        <ProductsServicesNotes>The main products or services were verified through reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</ProductsServicesNotes>
        <Certifications>
            <Certification>ISO 9001:2015</Certification>
            <CertificationSource>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</CertificationSource>
            <CertificationDate>Not available</CertificationDate>
            <CertificationNotes>The certification was verified through a reliable source, indicating a trustworthy certification.</CertificationNotes>
        </Certifications>
        <Certifications>
            <Certification>ISO 14001:2015</Certification>
            <CertificationSource>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</CertificationSource>
            <CertificationDate>Not available</CertificationDate>
            <CertificationNotes>The certification was verified through a reliable source, indicating a trustworthy certification.</CertificationNotes>
        </Certifications>
        <CertificationsOverviewNotes>The company has obtained relevant certifications, including ISO 9001:2015 and ISO 14001:2015, indicating a commitment to quality and environmental management.</CertificationsOverviewNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Textile</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</URL>
            <Source>https://squaregroup.com/bussiness/square-textiles-ltd/</Source>
            <URL>https://squaregroup.com/bussiness/square-textiles-ltd/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources are official company websites and business directories, which are considered reliable for industry information.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The industry classification was determined through reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with industry data.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions proposed for industry verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>No notes on industry verification, as the information was consistent and reliable across sources.</Notes>
        <IndustryTrendsNotes>No industry trends were noted, as the information was focused on the company's industry classification and products or services.</IndustryTrendsNotes>
        <CompetitivePositionNotes>No competitive position information was available, as the focus was on the company's industry classification and products or services.</CompetitivePositionNotes>
    </Industry>

    <OwnershipDetails>
        <ParentCompany>Square Group</ParentCompany>
        <ParentCompanyNotes>The parent company was verified through reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</ParentCompanyNotes>
        <Owner>Not available</Owner>
        <OwnershipStructureNotes>The ownership structure was not fully disclosed, but the parent company and key executives were verified through reliable sources.</OwnershipStructureNotes>
        <KeyDirectors>Mr. Tapan Chowdhury, Chairman; Mrs. Ratna Patra; Mr. Samuel S Chowdhury, Managing Director; Mr. Anjan Chowdhury; Mr. Abul Kalam Azad, Independent Director; Mr. Muhammadul Haque, Independent Director</KeyDirectors>
        <KeyDirectorsNotes>The key executives were verified through reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</KeyDirectorsNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Square Group</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</URL>
            <Source>https://squaregroup.com/bussiness/square-textiles-ltd/</Source>
            <URL>https://squaregroup.com/bussiness/square-textiles-ltd/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>Sources are official company websites and business directories, which are considered reliable for ownership information.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>The ownership details were verified through reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>OK</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No remaining issues with ownership data.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>No further actions proposed for ownership verification.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>OK</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>No notes on ownership verification, as the information was consistent and reliable across sources.</Notes>
        <BeneficialOwnershipNotes>No beneficial ownership information was available, as the focus was on the parent company and key executives.</BeneficialOwnershipNotes>
        <CorporateGovernanceNotes>No corporate governance information was available, as the focus was on the parent company and key executives.</CorporateGovernanceNotes>
    </OwnershipDetails>

    <FinancialInformation>
        <Revenue>Not available</Revenue>
        <RevenueNotes>No revenue information was available from the provided sources.</RevenueNotes>
        <ProfitBeforeTax>Not available</ProfitBeforeTax>
        <ProfitNotes>No profit information was available from the provided sources.</ProfitNotes>
        <MarketValue>Not available</MarketValue>
        <MarketValueNotes>No market value information was available from the provided sources.</MarketValueNotes>
        <StockInformation>Not available</StockInformation>
        <StockPerformanceNotes>No stock performance information was available from the provided sources.</StockPerformanceNotes>
        <ExactRawData>Not available</ExactRawData>
        <Sources>
            <Source>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</Source>
            <URL>https://textile.squaregroup.com/</URL>
        </Sources>
        <SourceNotes>The source is an official company website, but no financial information was available.</SourceNotes>
        <ChainOfThoughtReasoning>No financial information was available from the provided sources, indicating a need for further investigation.</ChainOfThoughtReasoning>
        <Status>NO_DATA</Status>
        <AnyRemainingIssues>No financial information was available from the provided sources.</AnyRemainingIssues>
        <ProposedNextSteps>Further investigation into alternative sources for financial information is proposed.</ProposedNextSteps>
        <SectionStatus>NO_DATA</SectionStatus>
        <Notes>No notes on financial data reliability, as no information was available from the provided sources.</Notes>
        <FinancialHealthNotes>No financial health assessment can be made, as no financial information was available from the provided sources.</FinancialHealthNotes>
        <FinancialReportingNotes>No financial reporting information was available from the provided sources.</FinancialReportingNotes>
    </FinancialInformation>

    <DataAssessmentSummary>
        <OverallDataQuality>Good</OverallDataQuality>
        <DataQualityNotes>The overall data quality is good, with most information verified through reliable sources, including official company websites and business directories.</DataQualityNotes>
        <MajorGaps>Registration number, financial information</MajorGaps>
        <DataGapsNotes>The registration number and financial information are significant gaps in the data, which may impact the overall assessment and decision-making.</DataGapsNotes>
        <RecommendedNextSteps>Further investigation into alternative sources for the registration number and financial information is recommended.</RecommendedNextSteps>
        <NextStepsNotes>The next steps should prioritize filling the gaps in the data, particularly the registration number and financial information, to ensure a comprehensive assessment.</NextStepsNotes>
        <Notes>No notes on the data collection process, as the information was compiled from the provided sources.</Notes>
        <ResearchProcessNotes>The research process involved compiling information from the provided sources, including official company websites and business directories.</ResearchProcessNotes>
        <ConfidenceLevelNotes>The confidence level in the data is good, with most information verified through reliable sources, but the gaps in the data may impact the overall confidence.</ConfidenceLevelNotes>
        <FinalRecommendationNotes>No final recommendation can be made, as the data gaps may impact the overall assessment and decision-making.</FinalRecommendationNotes>
    </DataAssessmentSummary>
</CompanyData>